promocodeslady.com 2016-10-30

# Privacy Policy - Promo Codes 2016

At **[PromoCodesLady.com](http://promocodeslady.com/)** ****, We consider the privacy of our visitors and readers to be extremely important and this is the privacy policy document describes all type of personal information and other details collected and recorded by **http://PromoCodesLady.com/** and how we use it.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
**Promo Codes Lady** does not use any cookies to store information about visitors’ preferences, to record user-specific information on which pages the site visitor accesses or visits, But we uses certain advertisers and traffic tracking tools that might uses the cookies in our web page content based upon visitors’ browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, **http://PromoCodesLady.com/** uses and create of log files. These files merely logs visitors on our site – usually a standard procedure for hosting companies and a part of hosting services’s analytics. The information inside the log files includes IP addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. This information is used to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
→ Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on _http://PromoCodesLady.com/_ from their Adsense and Affiliate network.  
→ Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our site’s visitors based upon their visit to _http://PromoCodesLady.com/_ and other sites on the Internet.  
→ Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

**Advertising Partners of PromoCodesLady.com :-**  
Below are the list of some of our advertising partners that might use cookies and web beacons on our site.

  * Google Adsense
  * Google Affiliate Network (GAN)
  * Commission Junction
  * Amazon
  * Clickbank
  * Linkshare
  * Yahoo! Publisher Network
  * Chitika
  * Infolinks
  * DoubleClick

_While each of these advertising partners has their own Privacy Policy for their site.  
You may consult this listing to find the privacy policy for each of the advertising partners of **http://PromoCodesLady.com/**._

We has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

**Third Party Privacy Policies**  
You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. http://PromoCodesLady.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.  
If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

**Consent**  
By using our website, you hereby consent to our privacy policy and agree to its terms.

**Update**  
This Privacy Policy was last updated on: Tuesday, February 22nd, 2013.
